https://incinolet.com/privacy/

Skip to content
Incinolet.com Privacy Policy
Incinolet.com is dedicated to protecting users’ privacy and protecting your personal information from misuse. We strongly support a policy of openness about personal data collection and use. We have created and implemented a policy that protects the use of any personally identifiable information (your name, e-mail address, snail mail address, telephone number). Like many websites, we collect information from users to constantly improve the site and provide more individualized content and advertising to them, but we only do so based on the guidelines stated in this policy. To make this privacy policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Please take note that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. This privacy statement does not cover the information practices of those web sites linked to Incinolet.com. We encourage you to review the statements of those sites.
What information does Incinolet.com collect?
Incinolet.com’s registration, online surveys, and newsletter forms may call for users to provide their contact information (like their name and e-mail address), and demographic information.
Incinolet.com uses the standard “cookie” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store data about your visit. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. We also may use cookies to track visits on Incinolet.com and the number of entries in some of our promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. Advertising networks that serve ads onto Incinolet.com may also use their own cookies. The cookie stores your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit and granting you certain access privileges. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password. We will not be able to customize the site’s features.
Incinolet.com may also gather anonymous information, which may be used by us or shared with third parties. This is information that does not personally identify you, but which may be helpful. For example, we might tell our advertisers how many users visited a particular advertisement, and for how long, so they can measure whether the ad worked. This information is also used to generate advertising rates. Generally, this information is collected through “traffic data” and may entail the use of numeric codes used to identify a computer.
What does Incinolet.com do with collected information?
Incinolet.com’s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our site. This includes personalization services, interactive communications, online shopping, and many other types of services, most of which are completely free to you. In order to provide services free of charge, we display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, Incinolet.com is able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you. This, in turn, helps us create a better website.
By delivering targeted advertisements, Incinolet.com allows advertisers to reach a targeted audience. From time to time, advertisers on Incinolet.com will seek to reach specific segments of our audience (e.g. females 35 and older). We will take the advertisement and display it to users meeting those criteria. This kind of advertisement targeting is done with banner ads as well as promotional email.
We use customer contact information from our online registration, surveys, promotions, giveaways, contests, and order forms for tracking purposes, our own internal evaluation, and to send you information from our company. Information collected as part of a contest, survey, promotion, or giveaway will be maintained for a minimum of 120 days beyond the end date of the event. After 120 days, the information may be destroyed or kept at the company’s discretion. From time to time, our business partners or other companies may send you promotional material. If you supply contact information, it may also be used to contact you about products and services in which you have indicated an interest, and may be shared with our advertisers, business partners, or other companies who may want to contact you. (Users may opt out of receiving future mailings — see the choice/opt-out section below.)
We may use cookies to deliver to you content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. Advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by advertisers on our site.
Incinolet.com may use your IP address (the number assigned to your computer while it is on the Internet) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site. At a point in time, when Incinolet.com offers shopping, your IP address may be used to help identify your computer and your online “shopping cart” (if any) and to gather broad demographic information. In addition, your IP address is transmitted with each message sent from your account.
Demographic and profile data from online forms or cookies may be used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content preferences you have previously shared with us. This information may be shared with our advertisers, business partners, or other companies only on an aggregate basis, unless you specifically agree that personally identifiable information about you may be disclosed.
If you submit financial information it may be used to verify the accuracy of your contact information and to authorize Incinolet.com to bill you for products and services you have agreed to purchase. You may choose to submit unique identifiers (such as order numbers) in order to allow us to verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Incinolet.com may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Incinolet.com or its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Incinolet.com or the users of Incinolet.com, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Incinolet.com or the public.
Security
Incinolet.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of any information we have collected from you. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. As you may realize, unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Incinolet.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. To further protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Children
Incinolet.com is a general audience site. Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We do not direct any of our content specifically at children less than thirteen (13) years of age. Further, we do not collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under thirteen (13) years of age.
Choice/Opt-Out
Incinolet.com gives you the following options for removing your information from our database in order to stop receiving future communications from Incinolet.com. (Please note: Incinolet.com is not responsible for removing information from third-party lists or entities with which you have previously authorized us to share your information.)
Contacting Incinolet, Inc.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Incinolet.com, please feel free to contact us:
You can send e-mail to: contactus@incinolet.com You can send mail to the following postal address:
Incinolet.com, Inc.
2639 Andjon,
Dallas, Texas 75220
Please recognize that any of the policies or procedures above may be changed at any time without prior notice. Although this Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights, it does serve as an expression of Incinolet.com’s commitment to protecting private personal information.
AllLiners and AccessoriesPartsShirtsToilets
Search for:
Lost your password?
Register
Email address *
Password *
Register
